{
    "1": {
        "question": "Containers contain an entire operating system.",
        "answer": "F"
    },
    "2": {
        "question": "Why is AWS more economical than traditional data centers for applications with varying compute workloads?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Amazon EC2 Costs are billed on a monthly basis.",
            "B": "Customers can permanently run enough instances to handle peak workloads.",
            "C": "Customers retain full administrative access to their Amazon EC2 instances.",
            "D": "Amazon EC2 instances can be launched on-demand when needed."
        },
        "answer": "D"
    },
    "3": {
        "question": "Which of the following must be specified when launching a new Amazon Elastic Cloud Compute EC2 windows instance?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Password for the administrator account.",
            "B": "Amazon Machine Image (AMI).",
            "C": "Amazon EC2 instance type.",
            "D": "The Amazon EC2 Instance ID."
        },
        "answer": "B"
    },
    "4": {
        "question": "If your project requires monthly reports that iterate through very large amounts of data, which Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud EC2 purchasing option should you consider?",
        "options": {
            "A": "On-Demand Instances.",
            "B": "Spot Instances.",
            "C": "Scheduled Reserved Instances.",
            "D": "Dedicated Hosts."
        },
        "answer": "C"
    },
    "5": {
        "question": "Which of the following services is a serverless compute service in AWS?",
        "options": {
            "A": "AWS OpsWork.",
            "B": "AWS Config.",
            "C": "AWS Lambda.",
            "D": "Amazon EC2."
        },
        "answer": "C"
    },
    "6": {
        "question": "Which Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud EC2 feature ensures your instances will not share a physical host with instances from any other AWS customer?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Placement Groups.",
            "B": "Amazon VPC.",
            "C": "Reserved Instances.",
            "D": "Dedicated Instances."
        },
        "answer": "D"
    },
    "7": {
        "question": "Which Amazon EC2 option is best for long-term workload with predictable usage patterns?",
        "options": {
            "A": "On-Demand Instances.",
            "B": "Reserved Instances.",
            "C": "Spot Instances."
        },
        "answer": "B"
    },
    "8": {
        "question": "What is included in an Amazon Machine Image (AMI)? Select the best answer.",
        "options": {
            "A": "All of the above.",
            "B": "A block device mapping that specifies the volumes to attach to the instance when it's launched.",
            "C": "Launch permissions that control which AWS accounts can use the AMI to launch instances.",
            "D": "A template for the root volume for the instance."
        },
        "answer": "A"
    },
    "9": {
        "question": "Your web application needs four instances to support steady traffic all of the time. On the last day of the month, the traffic triples. What is the most cost-effective way to handle this pattern?",
        "options": {
            "A": "Run four Reserved Instances constantly, then add eight On-Demand Instances on the last day of each month.",
            "B": "Run four On-demand Instances constantly, then add eight more On-Demand on the last day of each month.",
            "C": "Run 12 reserved instances all of the time.",
            "D": "Run four On-Demand Instances constantly, then add eight Reserved Instances on the last day of each month."
        },
        "answer": "A"
    },
    "10": {
        "question": "What is the service provided by AWS that enables developers to easily deploy and manage applications in the cloud?",
        "options": {
            "A": "AWS Elastic Beanstalk.",
            "B": "AWS OpsWork",
            "C": "Amazon Elastic Container Service.",
            "D": "AWS CloudFormation"
        },
        "answer": "A"
    }
}